

Expertise Skill

- Flutter / Firebase
- Python (Flask, Django)
- HTML/CSS/TS
- Angular/SQL
- Docker / Git / Mongo

Education

- 2019-2020 Lycée Mixte - Sidi Bouzid Bachelor of Computer Science
- 2023-2024 Bachelor Degree in Computer Science

Work Experience

- Flutter Developer Technopole Manouba | 2022-2023
 - design and development of a mobile application management of electronic products on the cloud
- PFE Internship

Faculty of Medecine. | 2023 - present

• Collect and analyze relevant medical data, contributing to the creation of prediction algorithms based on this data.

About Me

22-year-old computer science student from Monastir, Tunisia, about to graduate with a bachelor's degree. Passionate about problem solving, mobile development, cloud-computing and cyber security.

Contact Me

- +216 23 566 502
- hafedhgunichi@gmail.com
- hafedh-gunichi-d749f.web.app
- Stah Jabeur, Monastir, Tunisie



About me

22-year-old computer science student from Moanstir, Tunisia, about to graduate with a bachelor's degree. Passionate about problem solving and mobile development.

Contact Me

- +216 23 566 502
- hafedhgunichi@gmail.com
- hafedh-gunichi-d749f.web.app
- 🚫 Stah Jabeur, Monastir, Tunisie

FLUTTER DEVELOPER **Certificates**

- Machine Learning
- Coursera
- Google IT Automation with Python
- Professional Certificate Coursera
- Django
- Udemy
- Flutter
- Udemy
- Cyber-Security
- Udemy

Projects

- Jumia Scrapping
- Python, BS4, Selenium
- Instagram Clone
- Flutter, Firebase
- Cyber ISIMM
- Python, Flutter, Firebase
- Professional Portfulio
- Flutter
- Club Recruitment Form
- HTML, Bootstrap, Angluar, Firebase